UNITE Legislative Department Records 6000/007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Trade: WTO Get Out Vote, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Trade: WTO 5 Year Report, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Trade: WTO 1999 Ministerial (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Trade: WTO Post Seattle, 1998-2000 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- WTO Seattle Press, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Trade: WTO Singapore Meeting December 1996 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Trade - WTO - Textile Complaints, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Invest in America Now, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Jewish Labor Committee Resolutions, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1997-1999 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Nat. Women's Political Caucus, 1987-1990 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- ACTWU Companies - Brown Shoe 1994 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- ACTWU Companies - Fojtasek Company 1994 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- ACTWU Companies: Fojtasek Antonio Yanez Statement 3/95, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- ACTWU Companies - Fruit of the Loom 1994 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- ACTWU Companies - Leader 1994 Dyeing and Finishing (Box 20, Folder 27)
- ACTWU Companies Levi Strauss, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Levi Strauss Standards (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Levi Strauss Partnership Agreement 1994 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- ACTWU Comp. - Levi Strauss & ACTWU Partnership Letter 10/94, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- ACTWU Companies - Levi Strauss Wall Street Journal Art. 7/94, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- ACTWU Companies: Lodi Explosion (Lodi, NJ) 1995 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- ACTWU Companies - Londontown Corp. (London Fog) 1994 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- ACTWU Companies - Mid Atlantic Region w/ Cong. Representatives, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- ACTWU Companies - Pawnee Pants 1995 (Box 20, Folder 36)
- ACTWU Companies - Sara Lee Corp. 1994 (Box 20, Folder 37)
- ACTWU Companies - Tultex 1994 (Box 20, Folder 38)
- Auto Parts Division, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 39)
- Crafted with Pride in U.S.A., 1983-1985 (Box 20, Folder 40)
- Demo Convention, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 41)
- Histadrut, 1981-1986 (Box 20, Folder 42)
- Labor Advisory Committee on Trade Negotiations, 1995-1999 (Box 20, Folder 43)
- Letter to the Editor, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 44)
- LICIT - Labor Industry Coalition for International Trade, 1988-1995 (Box 20, Folder 45)
- National Women's Party, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 46)
- Re-invest in America, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 47)
- Unite Reception/Demo Convention August 1996 (Box 20, Folder 48)
- Admin. Code of Conduct, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Codes of Conduct, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- CTC, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Kennedy Speech - on Free Trade, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- CTC Legis. Strategy, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Deceptive Product Labeling, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Trade - Dr. Herman Starobin's Memos, 1992-1995 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Dr. Starobin's Testimony, 1993-1997 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- ILGWU, Campaign for Justice, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- "Model Agreement" - San Francisco, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Model Garments, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Model Garment Legislation, 1988-1993 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Olympic Team Uniforms, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Rules of Origin, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Strikes, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Strikes - Domsey, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Maidenform Strike, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Strikes Rainfair, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Testimony - Misc. 1 of 2, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Testimony - Misc. 2 of 2, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Testimony - 1 of 2, 1982-1984 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Testimony - 2 of 2, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Trade Background: 1987 OTA Study (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Trade Background: Multifiber Arrangement 1980-1984 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Trade Background: Impact on Canada, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Trade - CBI - 104th Congress, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Votes 102nd Congress 90-91, 1990-1993 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Voting Records 103rd Congress 1993 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Warn Act, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Caribbean Basin: Legislation Textile Amendment, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- "Endangered Labor Market" article by Evelyn Dubrow and H. Starobin, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Gephardt Amendment 1987 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- H.R. 3 (Economic Policy Reform Act of 1987) (Box 22, Folder 4)
- HR 1562 Veto Override Vote, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- HR 1562 - House Votes 1985 - 1986 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- ILGWU Research Reports, 1990-1995 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Labeling/Antidumping, 1977-1986 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Sweatshop: American Apparel Manufacturers Assoc. (AAMA), 1998 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Sweatshop: Campus, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Sweatshops: Cities, 1996-1998 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Sweatshops - Clean Clothes Campaign, 1996-2000 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Sweatshop: Cost vs. Price, 1993-1997 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Sweatshops: Curriculum, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Textile Trade: 1962-1985 Article, CR,, Reports, Etc. (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Trade: CBI Testimony, 1988-1990 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Trade: Customs Fraud, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- 1985 - Trade Legislation (Box 22, Folder 18)
- 1986 Trade Legislation (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Trade: News Articles 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Trade: Research (Reports and Studies) 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Trade 1987 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Trade Reports - 87 - 88, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Trade: Testimony HR.1154, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Trade: Testimony 1985-1986 Labor (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Trade: HR1562 - Cong. Record and Press Releases 1985 Vote (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Trade - Fitt VACC Plan for Economic Integration, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Trade: HR1154/S 549 Votes 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Trade: Media HR1154/S 549, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Exports, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Trade Anti-NAFTA Cong. Activity, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Clinton on Trade, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- China 104th Congress - Trade, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- China MFN - 103rd Congress, 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- MFN - Votes 102nd Congress, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- MFN for China 102nd Congress, 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- GSP, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Job Loss to Mexico, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- ILG Reports on Moves to Mex., 1993 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- NAFTA: Impact on States and Locations, 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- NAFTA Testimony, 1990-1993 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Trade - NAFTA - 103rd Congress, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- NAFTA + Women, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Trade - Organization Positions on NAFTA, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Trade Judge Richey Decision on NAFTA, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Trade - Mickey Kantor, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Trade + Human Rights, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Trade & Workers Rights, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- NAFTA + African Americans, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- IIE Study, 1992-1994 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- NAFTA ILG Job Loss, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- CIT Trade Watch, Membership List + Contributions, 1993-1995 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Riegle Resolution - S 109, 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Trade - USTR & Central America, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Trade and Exporting Jobs, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Trade - 104th Cong. Updates, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Trade/Saipan, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Various Reports on Trade, 1991-1993 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Waxman Resolution, 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- After NAFTA, 1994-1996 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Senator Carl Levin (D-MI), 1996 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Handgun Control, 1991-1995 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Hatch Amendment, 1990-1993 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Housing: Low Income/Homeless APWA, 1980-1989 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Haitian Refugee, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Haitians - Congressional Correspondence, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Highlights of Work Related Provisions of the 1990 IMM Act. (Box 24, Folder 7)
- ILGWU Comments on Immigration Regs--Employer Sanctions, 1987-1995 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Immigration Conference Benefits Issues, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Immigration-Misc. Issues-103rd Cong., 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Immigration-Labor Law Violations, 1993-1995 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Immigration Miscellaneous, 1986-1990 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Immigration-Naturalization "Ellis Island Group", 1990 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Immigration - Gilman - Conyer Letter, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Immigration - Conference Report Text, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Leslie Fay 1994 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- OSHA Senate Bill: S.1423, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- 104th OSHA - Unite Actions Testimony, Etc., 1995 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- 104th OSHA - Budget Matters, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- 104th OSHA - Clippings, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- 104th OSHA - HR 2725 - Evans Bill, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- 104th OSHA - Cooperative Programs, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- 104th OSHA - Fact Sheet, 1987-1996 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- 104th OSHA - Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- OSHA - Polling, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- OSHA - 104th Congress Senate-House Comparison (Box 24, Folder 26)
- 104th OSHA Task Force On, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- 104th OSHA - Votes, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- 104th OSHA - HR 1834-Ballenger Bill, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- OSHA Reform - 1992, 1989-1992 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- OSHA Reform, 103rd Congress, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- OSHA-Ballenger Bill HR 3234, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Pay Equity - 103rd Congress, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Pay Equity - 104th Congress House Bill H.R. 1507, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 34)
- Pay Equity Legislation, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- Pay Eg - Bill Bkgrnd., 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Fair Pay Act: S.232 105th Congress, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 37)
- Pay Equity - Harkin Bill, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 38)
- Raani Corp, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 39)
- Striker Replacement Acts, 1991-1995 (Box 24, Folder 40)
- Striker Replacement Corres., 1990-1993 (Box 24, Folder 41)
- Striker Replacement, 103rd Congress, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 42)
- S. 55 - 1994 Campaign (Box 24, Folder 43)
- (SR) Votes, Co-Sponsors & Bills HR 5 and s. 55, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 44)
- Salvadore, 1989-1991 (Box 24, Folder 45)
- State Legal Immigration Assistance Grant, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 46)
- Immigration Testimony, 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 47)
- Winnie Fashions Foreign Workers, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 48)
- Immigration Reform 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 49)
- 1976 ACTWU (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Canadian Free Trade, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- ILGWU, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Citizen Trade campaign-Press & Public Events, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- CTC - Materials, 1992-1995 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Coalition for Justice in the Maquiladors, 1990-1994 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Crime Bill, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- FastTrack, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- FFACT, 1990-1992 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Food Stamp - Buy Out, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Independent Contractors, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- LCCR Immigration Task Force Mailing List, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- I.M - 2/3 Issues, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- LCCR Immigration Task Force, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Group Legal Services, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- GSP - Dominican Republic, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Legal Services Legislation, 1990-1995 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Living Wage, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Maquiladoras 7/95, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Monitoring, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous Issues Telecommunications, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous Issues - 13, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Medicare & Medicaid 104th Congress, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Medicaid 104th Congress, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Medicaid - Graham Bill, 1996-1998 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Malden Mills Fire - 12/11/95, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- NAFTA + Latinos, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Persian Gulf - 1991 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- ILGWU, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- State Laws, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Takings, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Textile Votes, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Textile Bill Rally Info, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Textile and Apparel Footwear Act of 1990 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- 1973 ACTWU (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Trade-CTC - Outreach Task Force, 1993-1995 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Trade - Guatemala GSP Petition, 1994-1996 (Box 25, Folder 37)
- Trade - Trade Adjustment Assistance, 1993-1995 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Trade - Amerimex, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 39)
- Trade: Transshipments, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 40)
- ILG Convention Merger June 23, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Merger, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- ACTWU, ILGWU Merger: Press, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Merger Convention: UNITE Mission Statement 1995 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Jay Mazur - DNC info, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Merger Convention: Honduras & El Salvadoran guests info., 1995 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- UNITE Dental Benefits, 1996-2002 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- UNITE Memos, 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- UNITE's Newsletter for Uniformed Unions, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Women, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Women's Campaign Fund, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Women's Campaign Network (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Women's Legal Defense Fund, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- UNITE Organizing, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Women's Party Corp., 1992-1996 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Zensen Visit, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- UNITE Archives, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- UNITE Affiliate Contribution, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Charitable Giving (Box 27, Folder 3)
- UNITE - GEB 1996 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- GEB 2/97, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- GEB 6/24/97, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- GEB October 1997 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- GEB 2000 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- GEB 3/2001, 2000-2001 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- GIDC Grant, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- GEB Meeting 12/18/98, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- ILGWU Heritage Fund, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- UNITE! History, 1995-1998 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- UNITE Immigration Project, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- 1998-UNITE - Legislative Issues, 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- UNITE Legislative Priorities 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- UNITE Legislative Budget, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- UNITE Legislative Reports '98, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- UNITE Legislative Reports '97, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- UNITE Legislative Reports 1996 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- UNITE Convention: 1994, 1990-1995 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Unite Correspondence 1996 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- UNITE Correspondence 1997 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- 1998 Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 24)
- UNITE Communications 1999 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- UNITE Correspondence 2001 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- UNITE Correspondence (2003) (Box 27, Folder 27)
- UNITE - Fight, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- Florida Project, 1990-1991 (Box 27, Folder 29)
- UNITE! Legislative Conference, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- UNITE Lobby Forms, 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- UNITE Political & Legislative Conference June 9-14, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 32)
- UNITE Political Conference 1996, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 33)
- Reports on Int'l Dept., 1996 (Box 27, Folder 34)
- Republican Labor Council, 1988-1989 (Box 27, Folder 35)
- Save our Security Coalition, 1990-1991 (Box 27, Folder 36)
- Seniority, 1990-1991 (Box 27, Folder 37)
- Social Democrats, 1991-1993 (Box 27, Folder 38)
- Songs, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 39)
- Health - Managed Care Program, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 40)
- UNITE Pro, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 41)
- Sweatshop Campaign January 11 Event, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Sweatshops: David's Investigation, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Sweatshop: DOL Fashion Industry Forum, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Sweatshops: Child Labor, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Sweatshops: Interfaith Committee for Workers Rights, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Sweatshops: Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Sweatshop: Jay Mazur, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Sweatshop: Labeling Harkin Bill, 1996-1998 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Sweatshops: Op Ed - Linda Chavez Thompson, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Sweatshop Lobby Day Reports, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Immigration - Clippings, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Sweatshop: Marymount Conference: 5/30/97, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- May Company Sweatshop Report, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Sweatshops: Mazur Op Ed, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Sweatshops: Mother Jones Article, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Sweatshop: Newark Archdiocese, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Sweatshop: NCJW, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Sweatshop: North Olmsted, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Sweatshop: North Olmstead Patch, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Sweatshop: Nike, 1997-2001 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Sweatshops: Pennsylvania Bill, 1997-1999 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Sweatshop: Partnership Meeting 5/22/97, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Sweatshops: Pittsburgh, PA, 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Sweatshop: Pittsburgh, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Sweatshops: GAO Reports, 1988-1995 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Sweatshops - Publicity, 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- Sweatshops: Resolutions, 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- Sweatshops: Shopping Meetings, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- Sweatshops: Smithsonian Exhibition, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- 9/8 Smithsonian R.S.V.P 1998 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- Sweatshops: Speeches, Etc., 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- HR 90, Stop Sweatshops Act 1999 (Box 28, Folder 32)
- Sweatshops: Stop Sweatshops Act of 1996 (Box 28, Folder 33)
- Sweatshops: Stop Sweatshops Act Press Conference, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 34)
- Sweatshops: Student Stop Sweatshops, 1996-1999 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Federated Sweatshop Report (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Sweatshops: Unsorted File (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Sweatshop: UNITE Bill with DOL & Hill, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Sweatshops: UNITE Stop Sweatshop Lobby Day 7/29/98, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Sweatshop: United Students Against Sweatshops, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Sweatshop: UNITE Campaign, 1988-1995 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Sweatshop: UNITE Task Force, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Sweatshop: UNITE Involvement, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Sweatshop: UNITE Task Force Mtg. 12/5/97, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Sweatshop: UNITE Ltrs., 1997 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Sweatshop: UNITE Plan for 1998, 1997-1998 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Sweatshops: UNITE Central American Activity, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Sweatshops: UNITE Exhibit, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Sweatshops: UNITE Fact Sheets, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Sweatshops: UNITE Committee Meetings, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Sweatshop: UNTIE Sweatshop Summit, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Sweatshops - UNITE Bill, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Sweatshop: Victoria's Secret, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Sweatshops: US News Article, 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Sweatshops: Value City, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Sweatshops: Velazquez Budget Amendment, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Sweatshop: Video, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Sweatshops: Wal-Mart DNR, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Sweatshop Wal-Mart Kernaghan Report, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Wal-Mart: Ann Hoffman, 1993-1996 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Sweatshops: Warnaco, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- Sweatshops: Washington Post Series of Globalization, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 28)
- Sweatshop: Worker Rights Consortium, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 29)
- Sweatshop: World Bank, 1992-1995 (Box 29, Folder 30)
- Sweatshop: WTO Challenges, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 31)
- Sweatshop: Wu, Harry, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 32)
- 7/29 expenses, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 33)
- Follow Up, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 34)
- Phone, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 35)
- Hotel - Other Rooms, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 36)
- Choir + Hotel Rooms, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 37)
- Water, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 38)
- Dry Erase Boards (Communicaids) (Box 29, Folder 39)
- Tables, Chair Rental, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 40)
- Sound, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 41)
- Capital Police, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 42)
- Parking Lot, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 43)
- Van Rental, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 44)
- Translators, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 45)
- Uptown Caterers, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 46)
- Misc. Lobby Day, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 47)
- UNITE Folder & Papers, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 48)
- "Fighting Sweatshops at Home and Abroad" Presentation - Jay Mazur, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 49)
- Haiti -- Haiti After the Coup Report 1993 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Hoekstra, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Hoekstra Hearing, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Hoekstra 1999 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Hoekstra: 5/8 Hearing, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Hoekstra Hearing 3/31/98, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Hoekstra Hearing 9/25/98, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Hoekstra March 31, 1998 Hearing Committee Materials (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Corp. Campaigns - 104th Congress, 1996-1998 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Hoekstra: 1710 Notes (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Hoekstra: American Worker Project General, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Hoekstra: August 6 Hearing, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Hoekstra: Ann's Stuff, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Hoekstra: Attacks on Committee, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Hoekstra Hearing: Bankruptcy Matter, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Hoekstra: Background Campaign Contributors, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Hoekstra: Background Press, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Hoekstra: Background Voting Records, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Hoekstra: Chinatown, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Hoekstra Committee Report, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Hoekstra: Flannery Notes (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Hoekstra: Guess, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Hoekstra: June 1998 Hearing (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Hoekstra: Mademoiselle, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Hoekstra: Mademoiselle/Press, 1998-1999 (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Hoekstra: Mademoiselle Synewhouse, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 26)
- Hoekstra: Mademoiselle Prep Materials, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Hoekstra: Mademoiselle NLRB Materials, 1997-1998 (Box 30, Folder 28)
- Hoekstra: Mademoiselle Litigation Materials, 1997-1998 (Box 30, Folder 29)
- Hoekstra: Mademoiselle Clairborne Trademark Suit, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 30)
- NYC Compliance Report - 1 of 3, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- NYC Compliance Report - 2 of 3, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- NY Compliance Report - 3 of 3, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Hoekstra: Novak Column, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Hoekstra: Payroll Records, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Hoekstra Hearing L.A., 1998 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Hoekstra Press re 3/31/98, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Hoekstra: Republican Stuff Contacts, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Hoekstra: Teamsters Hearing, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Hoekstra Testimony 3/31/98, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Hoekstra: Translation Issue, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Hoekstra: UNITE Moves April/May 1998 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Hoekstra: UNITE Stuff, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Hoekstra - UNITE Testimony, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Labor - National Labor Committee Reports 1992 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Labor - Nat. Labor Committee Levi Strauss 1993 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Labor - Nat. Labor Committee Honduras/ Paraiso 1993 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- National Labor Committee Leslie Fay Workers Infor. 6/94, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Labor - National Labor 1994 Committee Dorka, Diaz, Lopez (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Labor: National Labor Relations Committee Orion 1995 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Labor: National Labor Relations Committee Mandarin 1995 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- Labor - Nat. Labor Committee Haiti 1993 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Matters with Jay Mazur (Box 31, Folder 23)
- IWPR Conference, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 24)
- DOW Corning Corporation: Bankruptcy, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 25)
- Yvonne Drawbaugh, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 26)
- "Assessing the Appropriateness of Rule Making at the U.S. Department of Labor" 5/8/88 Hearing, 1988-1998 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Pete Hoekstra, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO Documents, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- ACTWU-Testimony Before Congress, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- AARP Materials, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Congress - Accountability Act, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Contract with America, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Entitlements, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Gap Campaign, 1995-1996 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Hathaway Shirts, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Health Care - Kennedy, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Hobbs Act, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Background: IUD Resolutions 1996 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Homework 1993 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- ILO Conventions, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- ILO Conventions: Homework, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 14)